<article
    id="hello-world"
    created="Apr 17 2024"
    categoryId="behind-the-scenes"
    authorId="bakonpancakz"
    title="Hello World!"
    snippet="Breaking the radio silence what has bakonpancakz been up to? And what exactly is a suzzy?"
    banner="file://blog/hello-world/banner.gif"
    noindex="false"
>
    <header>Welcome to suzzy games!</header>
    <text> 
        I made this site to serve as a hub for my game development hobby. There
        is no theme, there is no incentive, just pure passion and efficient code. 
        I'll be sharing previews, progress, and generally whatever comes to mind. 
        So that's what this site is for! And this post contains a bunch of previews 
        of things I've worked on that <b>might</b> become their own game in the 
        future. 
    </text>
    <quote>Except for Cart Ride that one was just an update :P</quote>

    <!-- Game: Cart Ride around a Fumo -->
    <header>Cart Ride Around a Fumo</header>
    <text>
        <a href="https://www.roblox.com/games/9987852646/Cart-Ride-Around-a-Fumo">Cart Ride Around a Fumo</a> 
        is my own spin on the cart ride genre that was all over in the olden days
        of ROBLOX. It's a labor of love with way too much effort put into it, but
        I like to look back at it and try to match that level of quality for 
        everything I do.
    </text>
    <quote>Why Fumos? Because they're funny.</quote>
    <text>
        I spent a whole two months on it and again, put way more effort into it 
        than I should have, but that's just how I roll (⌐■_■). I actually got a 
        lot of my cousins to playtest it and everybody had a lot of fun blowing 
        each other up. Which I like to think is what kickstarted my passion. 
        <h>(my origin story)</h>
    </text>
    <image
        caption="Home Sweet Home"
        alt="Overhead view of the in-game track"
        resource="file://blog/hello-world/craf-1.jpeg"
    />
    <text> 
        Around ten people play it daily and people are still donating despite 
        its age, so I definitely did something right. (^_^) It even has a 
        couple videos on it, one of <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jjep6xt3PiM">friends just having fun</a>, 
        and a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fyoQxBuR1Mo">super duper edited one</a>. 
    </text>
    <quote>Thanks guys &lt;3</quote>
    <text>
        I actually planned to release a major update for it which would have added 
        cart customization and a track editor. But the update grew too large in 
        scope and is now being developed as its own standalone game. 
        <h>(stay tuned!)</h>
    </text>
    <text>
        It's nothing too interesting in my opinion but here's what one of the
        menus looked like.
    </text>
    <image
        caption="(Scrapped) Cart Selection Menu"
        alt="Screenshot of a scrapped concept showcasing cart customization"
        resource="file://blog/hello-world/craf-2.jpeg"
    />

    <!-- Game: Five Nights at Kanye 2 -->
    <header>Five Nights at Kanye 2</header>
    <text> 
        The <a href="https://www.roblox.com/games/13051172029/Five-Nights-at-Kanyes-FNAK-CLASSIC">original FNAK</a>
        was made in only a few hours but my friends really liked the idea so I fleshed it
        out a bit more and released a <a href="https://www.roblox.com/games/11229358049/Five-Nights-at-Kanyes-FNAK">remastered version</a>
        just for fun. A few people liked it and sent me messages asking for a second
        entry so I actually worked on it for a bit. 
    </text>
    <image
        caption="Main Menu"
        alt="Main Menu for Five Nights at Kanyes 2, taking place in a dimly lit restaurant"
        resource="file://blog/hello-world/fnak-1.jpeg"
    />
    <image
        caption="Kanye's Mansion (Courtyard)"
        alt="Wide angle view of the courtyard in Kanye's Mansion"
        resource="file://blog/hello-world/fnak-2.jpeg"
    />
    <image
        caption="Kanye's Mansion (Overhead with Layout)"
        alt="Overhead view of Kanye's Mansion with each room labelled"
        resource="file://blog/hello-world/fnak-3.jpeg"
    />
    <text> 
        The story I had in mind was that this was a prequel to the first game, 
        and this was the night you broke into Kanye's house to steal DONDA 3 
        for Twitter clout <s>(now called x lol)</s>. Over the course of five 
        nights you <h>(and up to 3 other friends)</h> were supposed to collect 
        story items that would unlock another room after each night. 
    </text>
    <text>
        Kanye was also intended to have a better than average AI that would actively 
        hunt you down as you made mistakes. Something as small as leaving a light on
        would make him suspicious and have him start to slowly but surely hunt you 
        down <h>(working as a soft time limit)</h>. 
    </text>
    <text> 
        For some added suspense, the music changes as Kanye's suspicious level changes. 
        All the way from clueless to chasing you down. It is based on Kanye's track 
        <a href="https://open.spotify.com/track/3JWiDGQX2eTlFvKj3Yssj3">Closed on Sunday</a>
        and made by Dakota <h>(he'll get a proper shoutout later!)</h>
    </text>
    <audio name="FNAK Stage 1 - We are Here (Arrival)"              resource="file://blog/hello-world/FNAK_Stage_1.mp3"/>
    <audio name="FNAK Stage 2 - Something Isn't Right (Tracking)"   resource="file://blog/hello-world/FNAK_Stage_2.mp3"/>
    <audio name="FNAK Stage 3 - He's Near (Tracking, Close)"        resource="file://blog/hello-world/FNAK_Stage_3.mp3"/>
    <audio name="FNAK Stage 4 - Found you (Chasing)"                resource="file://blog/hello-world/FNAK_Stage_4.mp3"/>

    <!-- Game: Project Z -->
    <header>Project Z</header>
    <text> 
        Project Z is a <i>player-versus-player, first-person shooter, zombie survival</i> 
        game where you barricade yourself into a room and fight off zombified 
        players for six waves with each wave unlocking new zombie classes and
        zombie bosses. <h>Did you get all that?</h>
    </text>
    <text>
        I worked on a few systems <h>(UI, Social, Weapons, etc)</h> but never 
        got around to making an actual working prototype to fully test the 
        idea out. Even worse is that changes to ROBLOX suddenly broke my 
        scripts so I can't even show them off except for in this equally 
        terrible quality video.
    </text>
    <text>
        It's definitely a cool idea and I will most likely revisit it in the
        future and give the love it deserves. This idea actually borrows a ton
        from the original <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=105462463">Garry's Mod Zombie Survival</a> 
        which I used to play it all the time back in middle school and really
        wanted to bring the idea to modern audiences.
    </text>
    <video
        caption="Broken Weapons and Sprays"
        cover="file://blog/hello-world/ProjectZ-Cover.jpeg"
        resource="file://blog/hello-world/ProjectZ.mp4"
    />

    <!-- Section: The Plan -->
    <header>What now?</header>
    <text>
        Well, I'm going back to working on that standalone project I mentioned 
        earlier! It's called Project Monke and you can think of it as Super 
        Monkey Ball and Super Mario Maker put together. It has online services 
        <h>(which is why you can create an account btw)</h> so that should give
        you an idea of how large of a scope this project has.
    </text>
    <text>
        If you make an account there isn't really a whole lot you can do with it
        now, except for some profile customization and security related features. 
        I'll be adding comments to the site at a later date, but for now the 
        foundation has been set.
    </text>
    <image
        caption="And for all the nerds out there, the backend is written in Go, the frontend is hand-written PUG+CSS+JS, and served using NGINX, on my personal server (nicknamed miku)"
        alt="Picture of a computer stuffed in the closest with a Hatsune Miku sticker slapped in the corner"
        resource="file://blog/hello-world/peak-performance.jpeg"
    />

    <!-- Section: Special Thanks -->
    <header>Special Thanks to Dakota</header>
    <text> 
        Before I go, I'd also like to share a couple more tracks from Dakota 
        <s>who I have locked in my basement</s> who graciously offered to make 
        music for my projects. He also made the Five Nights at Kanye tracks you 
        heard earlier. <a href="https://soundcloud.com/user-627340075">Check out his Soundcloud!</a> ^_^ 
    </text>
    <audio name="Project Monke - Settings"      resource="file://blog/hello-world/ProjectMonke_Settings.mp3"/>
    <audio name="FNAK - Settings (Original)"    resource="file://blog/hello-world/FNAK_Options_Original.mp3"/>
    <audio name="FNAK - Settings (In-Game)"     resource="file://blog/hello-world/FNAK_Options_InGame.mp3"/>
    <video
        caption="inside joke :3"
        cover="file://blog/hello-world/settings-Cover.jpeg"
        resource="file://blog/hello-world/settings.mp4"
    />
    <quote>p.s. wanna leave an encouraging comment or question? Leave a comment on my twitter!</quote>
    <quote>p.p.s there's an easter egg hidden somewhere on this site for users, I hope you love picross as much as I do~</quote>
</article>