<article
    id="repo-of-knowledge"
    created="May 12 2024"
    categoryId="behind-the-scenes"
    authorId="bakonpancakz"
    title="Repo of Knowledge"
    snippet="Fresh paint, building libraries, and starting side-projects (again). Welcome to new suzzy games website!"
    banner="file://blog/repo-of-knowledge/banner.png"
    noindex="false"
>
    <!-- Introduction -->
    <header>A Fresh Coat of Paint</header>
    <text>
        <b>Welcome to the new and improved suzzy games website!</b>
    </text>
    <text>
        Absolutely everything on this site has been either upgraded or replaced
        entirely. The blog system went from janky to proper, pages are now full
        of content and trivia instead of being half-baked, and a new library was 
        built. <h>More on this later!</h> 
        I dedicated an entire weekend to turn this site from potato to french
        fry. I absolutely love how it looks now and I hope you do too. 
    </text>
    <quote>Sometimes I open up the website just to stare at it @_@</quote>
    <image
        caption="New and Improved!"
        alt="A 4 by 4 grid showing the old site on top and the new site design on the bottom"
        resource="file://blog/repo-of-knowledge/SITE_SHOWCASE.jpg"
    />

    <!-- New Feature: oAuth2 -->
    <header>Introducing oAuth2</header>
    <text>
        <b>Are you a developer? Then this chapter is for you!</b> Applications 
        and oAuth2 are now available for everybody! This allows third-party 
        developers to safely access your profile and the game data that 
        <b>you</b> decide to share with them.
    </text>
    <text>
        New features and subsequent documentation on those features will become 
        available for developers in the library. 
        <h>Which brings us to the next topic...</h>
    </text>
    <image
        caption="oAuth2 User Interface (You've seen one of these before right?)"
        alt="An example oAuth2 prompt asking the user to allow access to certain account permissions"
        resource="file://blog/repo-of-knowledge/OAUTH2_SHOWCASE.png"
    />

    <!-- New Feature: Developer Docs -->
    <header>Building a Library</header>
    <text>
        <a href='/library'>The library</a> is a new section of the suzzy website!
        It contains legal stuff, branding guidelines, and most importantly 
        documentation for developers. If you're really bored check out the 
        <a href="/library/home/branding" target="_blank">branding article</a>! 
        It contains little bits of trivia on all past suzzy projects.
    </text>
    <image
        caption="Library Homepage (Its Boo!)"
        alt="A preview for the suzzy games library with the mascot sitting on a bean bag in their room reading a book"
        resource="file://blog/repo-of-knowledge/LIBRARY_SHOWCASE.png"
    />

    <!-- Announcement: New 2D Game Engine -->
    <header>Introducing BECCA2D</header>
    <video
        caption="BECCA2D Splash Screen"
        resource="file://blog/repo-of-knowledge/BECCA2D_TEASER.mp4"
        cover="file://blog/repo-of-knowledge/BECCA2D_TEASER_COVER.png"
    />
    <text>
        <b>Introducing BECCA2D!</b> An <i>in-house 2D Game Engine</i> designed
        from the ground up to be lightweight, efficient, extensible, and run in
        Google Chrome. <h>sorry firefox users :p</h>
    </text>
    <text>
        I'm planning on using this engine in a new side-project, a side-scrolling
        style platformer fangame based on a certain fish vtuber I've taken a liking
        to recently. This fangame also shares a considerable amount of features with 
        Project Monke, so this will also serve as a personal training ground of sorts. 
    </text>
    <text>
        But that's all I'm sharing about this side-project for today! I'll be making 
        a dedicated post on the engine showcasing its features, design, and reasoning
        soon™
    </text>

    <!-- Summary -->
    <header>Epilogue</header>
    <text> 
        So that's my content dump for the month. Again I'm still working on new
        stuff and it'll all be done and released eventually 
        <h>gimme like six months or something :P</h>
    </text>
    <image
        caption="ok that's it see you soon™"
        alt="A man holding the ball standing in front a white board with the words soon trademarked"
        resource="file://blog/repo-of-knowledge/conclusion.png"
    />
    <quote>p.s. I got a drawing tablet! nothing crazy just a wacom one! expect more doodles all over the site now</quote>
    <quote>p.p.s still no blog comments btw >.></quote>
</article>